Patrick (Brien) Barr

Carmel, IN 46280 | Email: brien.barr3320@gmail.com | Phone: 317-910-6049

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/p-brien-barr-587ba8164 | GitHub: https://github.com/BrienBarr

Portfolio: https://brienbarr.github.io/Portfolio/

Summary

Experienced full stack developer with over 3 years experience creating interactive programs for museums and science centers. Over 10 years front end development experience with creating and maintaining corporate site. Adept in and executing strategies to complete projects on time and within budget. Works well in both a team and individual environment. Currently attending the Butler University Executive Coding Bootcamp.

Technical Skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, API, Node.js, PHP, Visual Studio Code, GitHub, Windows OS, Microsoft Office 365, Adobe Production Software (Premiere, Photoshop, After Effects, Dreamweaver, InDesign), Autodesk 3ds Max, Autodesk AutoCAD LT

Projects

What's for Dinner?

- Interactive app allowing user to search for and save meal and cocktail recipes while getting a random joke using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, local storage, and API calls.
- Deployed application: https://devoyno.github.io/food_drinks_jokes/
- GitHub repository: https://github.com/Devoyno/food drinks jokes

Weather Dashboard

- Interactive app allowing user to search for cities or recall from search history to get current weather and 5-day forecast using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, local storage, and API calls.
- Deployed application: https://brienbarr.github.io/Weather-Dashboard/
- GitHub repository: https://github.com/BrienBarr/Weather-Dashboard

Experience

Bowen Technovation

Indianapolis, IN

2002-Present

Promoted to: Full Stack Interactive Developer

2017-Present

Created and deployed user interactive experiences for museums and science centers

Promoted to: Website Creation and Maintenance

• Updated corporate website and created new web content for site

- Maintained all in-house computers, network, and printers
- Produced marketing materials for print and web
- Managed all audio/video/interactive content creation and deployment

Assistant Audio/Video Editor

2002-2003

2003-Present

· Assisted with all audio and video content editing

Education

Butler Executive Coding Bootcamp - Indianapolis, IN Certificate

Ball State University - Muncie, IN Graduated *Magna Cum Laude* BA Telecommunications/Production Minor in Film Studies